[ EMERGENCY ALERT](https://www.maricopa.gov/AlertCenter.aspx) [Evacuate/GO! - Evacuate Canyon Lake/Tortilla Flat area: Siphon Fire Read On...](https://www.maricopa.gov/AlertCenter.aspx?AID=EvacuateGO-Evacuate-Canyon-LakeTortilla--124)

1. [I Want To...](https://www.maricopa.gov/9/I-Want-To)
2. [Services](https://www.maricopa.gov/101/Services)
3. [Departments](https://www.maricopa.gov/27/Departments)

1. [Home](https://www.maricopa.gov/4/Home)
2. Site Terms & Privacy Policy

Site Terms & Privacy Policy
===========================

**Disclaimer** 
---------------

Terms of Use

Maricopa County attempts to maintain the highest accuracy of content; yet neither Maricopa County, nor any agency, officer, or employee of Maricopa County, warrants the accuracy, reliability or timeliness of any information published on this system. User shall hold Maricopa County harmless from and against any losses caused by reliance on the accuracy, reliability or timeliness of such information.

Information may be changed or updated without notice.  Maricopa County may make improvements and/or changes in the materials contained in or described on this web site at any time without notice.  Maricopa County may also make changes in this disclaimer without notice.  It is recommended that the user periodically visit this page to review the current Disclaimer.

Maricopa County's web site has links to other web sites, and not all of these have been reviewed.  Maricopa County is not responsible for the content of any off-site pages. These include links to web sites operated by other government agencies, nonprofit organizations and private businesses. When you follow a link to another web site, you are no longer on Maricopa County's web site and this disclaimer will not apply; and you are subject to the privacy policy of that new web site. When you follow a link to one of these web sites neither Maricopa County, nor any agency, officer, or employee of Maricopa County warrants the accuracy, reliability or timeliness of any information published on these external web sites, nor endorses any content, viewpoints, products, or services linked from these systems, and shall not be held liable for any losses caused by reliance on the accuracy, reliability or timeliness of such information.

Reference on this web site to any specific commercial products, processes, or services, or the use of any trade, firm, or corporation name is for the information and convenience of the public, and does not constitute endorsement, recommendation, or favoring by Maricopa County, or its employees or agents. When downloading information or items, it is the user's responsibility to take precautions to ensure that whatever is selected is free of viruses, worms, Trojan horses and other items of a destructive nature.

This disclaimer pertains to the Maricopa County web site as a whole. Sub sites of the Maricopa County web site may have additional disclaimers pertinent to the information they contain. It is recommended that all users refer to these disclaimers prior to accessing such sub sites.

Third Party App

Maricopa County is using SeeClickFix, an online and mobile service request system, to power its mobile app Notify MCDOT and reporting forms. SeeClickFix is an application that allows Maricopa County residents to report non-emergency roadway related issues. SeeClickFix can be used via the Web on a desktop computer, laptop, mobile phone, or tablet. SeeClickFix is a public application. The description entered will be visible to the public. Your display name will also be visible unless you choose to submit as Anonymous. Your email address will never be displayed publicly.

**Privacy Policy**
------------------

Privacy & Security Statement

All phone numbers and email addresses maintained by Maricopa County contain the names of people who voluntarily communicated with or requested information from Maricopa County. At present, phone numbers and email addresses or any personally identifying information about individuals are not sold or rented to any governmental, commercial, or other entities. When a user has given Maricopa County their phone number or email address for purposes of communicating with or requesting information from Maricopa County, that communication becomes a part of the public record and may be subject to disclosure under applicable Arizona and Federal statute(s).  
  
For security purposes and to ensure that this service remains available to all users, Maricopa County's website also employs measures to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information or otherwise cause damage.  
  
Unauthorized attempts to upload information or change information on this service are strictly prohibited and may be punishable under applicable Arizona and Federal statute(s).

1.   
    301 West Jefferson Street  
    Phoenix, Arizona 85003  
      
    Main Line:  [602-506-3011](tel: 602-506-3011)  

### [Using This Site](https://www.maricopa.gov/QuickLinks.aspx?CID=555)

1. [Sitemap](https://www.maricopa.gov/sitemap)
    
2. [Accessibility](https://www.maricopa.gov/Accessibility)
    
3. [Copyright Notices](https://www.maricopa.gov/site/copyright)
    
4. [Site Terms & Privacy Policy](https://www.maricopa.gov/124/Privacy-Policy)
    
5. [Home](https://www.maricopa.gov/)

/QuickLinks.aspx

### [Residents](https://www.maricopa.gov/QuickLinks.aspx?CID=558)

1. [Contact Us](https://www.maricopa.gov/5342/Staff-by-Common-Requests)
    
2. [Board Meetings and Agendas](https://www.maricopa.gov/324/Board-of-Supervisors-Meeting-Information)
    
3. [Organizational Chart](https://www.maricopa.gov/DocumentCenter/View/13710/County-Organizational-Chart?bidId=)
    
4. [Volunteer/Intern Opportunities](https://www.maricopa.gov/3901/Employment-Initiatives)
    
5. [Required Postings](https://www.maricopa.gov/3872/Required-Postings)

/QuickLinks.aspx

### [Visitors](https://www.maricopa.gov/QuickLinks.aspx?CID=554)

1. [About Maricopa County](https://www.maricopa.gov/5289/Maricopa-County)
    
2. [Quick Facts](https://www.maricopa.gov/3598/About-Maricopa-County)
    
3. [Economic Development](https://www.maricopa.gov/1618/Economic-Development)
    
4. [Working for Us](https://www.maricopa.gov/3776/Human-Resources)
    
5. [Newsroom](https://www.maricopa.gov/5350/County-News)

/QuickLinks.aspx

Loading

Loading

Do Not Show Again Close

Arrow Left Arrow Right

\[\]

Slideshow Left Arrow Slideshow Right Arrow
